Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪The flowers fall low into the dust♪
♪تسقط الزهور منخفضة في الغبار♪
♪Cannot see spring's fragile branches♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية فروع الربيع الهشة♪
♪Beneath Song City's blooms♪
♪تحت أزهار مدينة سونغ♪
♪I've no longer had a home♪
♪لم يعد لدي منزل♪
♪I will turn these years into poems♪
♪سأحول هذه السنوات إلى قصائد♪
♪Waiting for the flowers and full moon♪
♪في انتظار الزهور والقمر♪
♪Love and hate entwine, nothing owed♪
♪الحب والكراهية يتشابكان، لا شيء مستحق♪
♪All will drift away with the wind♪
♪كل شيء سوف ينجرف مع الريح♪
[The Sparrow's Gambit]
[مناورة العصفور]
[Episode 4]
[الحلقة 4]
Mr. Li,
السيد لي،
before we play,
قبل أن نلعب،
I have a new friend to introduce.
لدي صديق جديد أريد أن أقدمه.
This is...
هذا هو...
Miss Liu.
السيدة ليو.
[Mr. Li.]
[السيد لي.]
Seeing is believing.
نظرا لصدقه.
So you already knew Miss Liu.
لقد كنت تعرفين السيدة ليو بالفعل.
Miss Liu,
السيدة ليو،
since you're Wan'er's friend,
بما أنك صديق وان إير،
tonight,
الليلة،
the three of us
نحن الثلاثة
shall join Mr. Li for a fine game.
سوف انضم إلى السيد لي للعب مباراة رائعة.
How about it?
ماذا عن ذلك؟
A pleasure.
متعة.
Very well.
جيد جدا.
Come, please sit.
تعال، من فضلك اجلس.
Miss Liu, please.
السيدة ليو، من فضلك.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
You've had a drink.
لقد شربت.
Let me get it for you.
دعني أحصل عليه لك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Come on.
تعال.
I won again.
لقد فزت مرة أخرى.
My apologies.
اعتذاري.
Mr. Li, your luck tonight
السيد لي، حظك الليلة
is quite remarkable.
أمر رائع للغاية.
A gift for you, Miss Liu.
هدية لك يا آنسة ليو.
Mr. Li,
السيد لي،
these chips of yours
هذه الرقائق الخاصة بك
are in the way.
في الطريق.
I'll have them exchanged
سأقوم بتبادلهم
and sent to your home.
وأرسلت إلى منزلك.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
The Chamber matter
مسألة الغرفة
is troublesome.
أمر مزعج.
Vice President Zhou has always had you cornered
لقد كان نائب الرئيس تشو دائمًا يحاصرك
with perfume.
مع العطر.
Besides,
بجانب،
you now have
لديك الآن
the Blycher Hotel incident.
حادثة فندق بليشر.
Hard to say.
من الصعب أن أقول.
Mr. Li,
السيد لي،
Blycher Hotel isn't ours.
فندق بليشر ليس فندقنا.
No real effect.
لا يوجد تأثير حقيقي.
That depends on your father's choice.
هذا يعتمد على اختيار والدك.
Let us try something new.
دعونا نحاول شيئا جديدا.
Time for one last game.
حان وقت اللعبة الأخيرة.
I'll sit out.
سأجلس بالخارج.
These two ladies will keep you company.
هاتان السيدتان سوف تبقيان معك.
Winner takes all.
الفائز يأخذ كل شيء.
The loser
الخاسر
will escort Mr. Li home.
سوف يرافق السيد لي إلى منزله.
How about it,
ماذا عن ذلك؟
Mr. Li?
السيد لي؟
Dad.
أب.
Very well.
جيد جدا.
A refined pastime.
هواية راقية.
At my age,
في عمري،
I enjoy such elegance.
أستمتع بهذه الأناقة.
Good idea.
فكرة جيدة.
Let me deal.
دعني أتعامل.
Mr. Li.
السيد لي.
Wan'er.
وانر.
Miss Liu.
السيدة ليو.
Mr. Li, you first.
السيد لي، أنت أولاً.
My apologies.
اعتذاري.
Wan'er,
وانر،
show your hand.
أظهر يدك.
Smaller than mine.
أصغر مني.
Miss Liu,
السيدة ليو،
your turn.
دورك.
your hand is even smaller.
يدك أصغر أيضًا.
You lost.
لقد خسرت.
Here's to you.
إليك.
Wine alone is useless.
النبيذ وحده لا فائدة منه.
Mr. Wang, will you honor your word?
السيد وانغ، هل ستحترم كلمتك؟
A bet is a bet.
الرهان هو الرهان.
I'll finish this to show my respect.
سأنهي هذا لإظهار احترامي.
Thousand-Step Scent?
رائحة الألف خطوة؟
What?
ماذا؟
Thousand-Step Scent.
رائحة الألف خطوة.
Miss Liu, that perfume you're wearing
آنسة ليو، هذا العطر الذي ترتدينه
is that Thousand-Step Scent
هل هذه رائحة الألف خطوة؟
everyone says lingers on the skin?
الجميع يقولون أنه يبقى على الجلد؟
Miss Liu,
السيدة ليو،
where did it come from?
من أين جاء؟
This formula
هذه الصيغة
was tucked
كان مدسوسًا
in a book
في كتاب
I bought overseas.
لقد اشتريت من الخارج.
And I had a friend
وكان عندي صديق
make a bottle
اصنع زجاجة
with this formula.
مع هذه الصيغة.
I like the scent.
أنا أحب الرائحة.
If you like it,
إذا أعجبك ذلك،
I'll find the formula
سأجد الصيغة
and send it tomorrow.
وأرسله غدا.
Indeed.
بالفعل.
Having Rumeng come today
لقد جاء رومينج اليوم
was a happy accident.
لقد كان حادثًا سعيدًا.
It shows you and the scent
إنه يظهر لك والرائحة
are destined.
مقدر.
Her company can wait.
شركتها يمكن أن تنتظر.
A rare scent must be taken today.
رائحة نادرة يجب أن نأخذها اليوم.
Mr. Wang,
السيد وانغ،
you are thoughtful.
أنت متفكر.
Then I shall congratulate you here.
ثم سأهنئكم هنا.
You are the leader of the perfume industry.
أنت قائد صناعة العطور.
You flatter me.
أنت تملقني.
Miss Liu,
السيدة ليو،
I'll be at home tomorrow,
سأكون في المنزل غدا
looking forward to your visit.
نتطلع إلى زيارتكم.
Do not forget.
لا تنسى.
Mr. Li, take care.
السيد لي، اعتني بنفسك.
I shall leave as well.
سأغادر أيضاً.
Miss Liu, please stay.
السيدة ليو، من فضلك ابقي.
You are
أنت
Wan'er's friend,
صديق وان إير،
and that makes you a friend to the Wang family.
وهذا يجعلك صديقًا لعائلة وانج.
We hope to see you here often.
نأمل أن نراكم هنا كثيرًا.
Of course.
بالطبع.
I shall go now.
سأذهب الآن.
Take care.
يعتني.
Still here?
هل لازلت هنا؟
You waited for me.
لقد انتظرتني.
Aren't you afraid they will see you?
ألا تخاف أن يرونك؟
The scent.
الرائحة.
Miss Liu,
السيدة ليو،
your Thousand-Step Scent and your burn scar...
رائحة خطواتك الألف وندبة الحروق الخاصة بك...
Wish to know me, huh?
تريد أن تعرفني، أليس كذلك؟
Control your curiosity.
تحكم في فضولك.
Meng,
منغ،
you must not use perfume.
لا يجوز لك استخدام العطر.
This scar rose
ارتفعت هذه الندبة
from the perfume's sting.
من لسعة العطر.
The Lin family
عائلة لين
lives by perfume.
يعيش بالعطر.
Yet you
ومع ذلك انت
can never craft it again.
لن أستطيع صنعه مرة أخرى أبدًا.
Every scar on me
كل ندبة علي
reminds me of what I've done wrong.
يذكرني بما فعلته خطأً.
I shall send each Wang
سأرسل لكل وانغ
to heck myself,
لأعذب نفسي
and tear off their false masks.
وتمزيق أقنعتهم الكاذبة.
Hua, check Chen Wenbin.
هوا، تحقق من تشين وينبين.
Did he tell them about you?
هل أخبرهم عنك؟
He knows Qingmao too well.
إنه يعرف تشينغماو جيدًا.
I have to check him out.
يجب علي التحقق منه.
Can't let him ruin my plan.
لا أستطيع أن أسمح له بتدمير خطتي.
If he serves the Wangs,
إذا كان يخدم عائلة وانغ،
he is not innocent.
إنه ليس بريئا.
The auction order and funds
أمر المزاد والأموال
are set for tomorrow.
تم تحديدها للغد.
Blycher Hotel and Marshal Chen
فندق بليشر ومارشال تشين
will be yours.
ستكون لك.
Only by provoking Wang Wan'er
فقط من خلال استفزاز وانغ وان إير
can our plan proceed smoothly.
هل يمكن أن تسير خطتنا بسلاسة؟
About
عن
Liu Rumeng,
ليو رومينج,
have you checked her?
هل قمت بفحصها؟
She, a singer's daughter,
هي ابنة مغنية
was taken overseas by Hua's man
تم نقله إلى الخارج بواسطة رجل هوا
and has only returned recently.
وقد عاد مؤخرا فقط.
All records are clear.
جميع السجلات واضحة.
As for the perfume formula,
أما بالنسبة لتركيبة العطر،
I've seen it.
لقد رأيته.
It was indeed in the book.
لقد كان في الكتاب بالفعل.
How did the Lin family's
كيف كانت عائلة لين
Thousand-Step Scent reach overseas?
هل تصل رائحة الألف خطوة إلى الخارج؟
And Blycher Hotel's raid...
ومداهمة فندق بليشر...
These matters
هذه الأمور
are not so simple.
ليست بهذه البساطة.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
Blycher Hotel will be secretly auctioned.
سيتم عرض فندق بليشر للبيع في مزاد سري.
Too many secrets inside.
هناك الكثير من الأسرار في الداخل.
Arrange it well.
رتبها جيدا.
We must win the hotel,
يجب علينا الفوز بالفندق
then destroy every trace.
ثم قم بتدمير كل أثر.
[Blycher Hotel]
[فندق بليشر]
[Lot]
[كثير]
Our first lot today
أول قطعة لدينا اليوم
is Blycher Hotel.
هو فندق بليشر.
It was built by
تم بناؤه بواسطة
a European designer.
مصمم أوروبي.
Blycher Hotel holds Wang Penghui's opium-dealing records.
يحتفظ فندق بليشر بسجلات تجارة الأفيون الخاصة بوانغ بينجهوي.
At this secret auction,
في هذا المزاد السري،
whoever's against the Wang family
من هو ضد عائلة وانغ
will show up.
سوف تظهر.
He must know Qingmao's whereabouts.
لا بد أنه يعرف مكان تواجد تشينغماو.
The highest bidder is
أعلى مزايد هو
Number Seven.
رقم سبعة.
Where is Seven?
أين سبعة؟
Seven is here.
سبعة هنا.
Congratulations, ma'am.
مبروك سيدتي.
The second lot in today's auction
القطعة الثانية في مزاد اليوم
was personally consigned by its owner.
تم تسليمها شخصيا من قبل مالكها.
The lot is
القطعة هي
a kiss from Marshal Chen.
قبلة من المارشال تشين.
Wenbin?
وينبين؟
Nobody move!
لا أحد يتحرك!
I bid 100,000 silver coins.
أعرض 100 ألف قطعة فضية.
Any advance on this?
أي تقدم في هذا الشأن؟
Do I hear another bid?
هل أسمع عرضا آخر؟
Marshal Chen.
المارشال تشين.
Congratulations to Number one,
مبروك للرقم واحد
- the sole bidder. - The Blycher Hotel is mine.
- المزايد الوحيد. - فندق بليشر ملكي.
So are you.
وأنت كذلك.
♪The flowers fall low into the dust♪
♪تسقط الزهور منخفضة في الغبار♪
♪Cannot see spring's fragile branches♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية فروع الربيع الهشة♪
♪Beneath Song City's blooms♪
♪تحت أزهار مدينة سونغ♪
♪I've no longer had a home♪
♪لم يعد لدي منزل♪
♪Magnolia petals fly across the sky♪
♪بتلات الماغنوليا تطير عبر السماء♪
♪Spring and autumn come and go♪
♪الربيع والخريف يأتيان ويذهبان♪
♪People gather and part♪
♪يتجمع الناس ويفترقون♪
♪How brave can one be with no regrets?♪
♪كيف يمكن للإنسان أن يكون شجاعًا دون أن يشعر بالندم؟♪
♪I will paint love and hate in the sky♪
♪سأرسم الحب والكراهية في السماء♪
♪Engraving my love for you♪
♪نقش حبي لك♪
♪I roam through this chaotic world♪
♪أتجول في هذا العالم الفوضوي♪
♪Who will guard me for life?♪
♪من سيحرسني طيلة حياتي؟♪
♪I will turn these years into poems♪
♪سأحول هذه السنوات إلى قصائد♪
♪Waiting for the flowers and full moon♪
♪في انتظار الزهور والقمر♪
♪Love and hate entwine, nothing owed♪
♪الحب والكراهية يتشابكان، لا شيء مستحق♪
♪All will drift away with the wind♪
♪كل شيء سوف ينجرف مع الريح♪